A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE STUDY CLUB, 1954 - 1955, TDoc (6), TL (3) (Box-folder 050:008)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN TV & RADIO MATERIALS, 1960 - 1964, AL, TL (32), TMemo (10), TDoc (12) (Box-folder 050:009)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE TV AND RADIO MATERIALS, 1954 - 1959, TL, TDoc (8), TMemo (3) (Box-folder 050:010)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN TIE-TIE PRODUCTS, 1952 - 1964, TDoc (4), TMemo (9), TL (13) (Box-folder 050:011)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE - WORKSHOPS, 1953 - 1956, TDoc (4), TL (2) (Box-folder 050:012)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN - GENERAL, 1970 - 1980, TDoc (22), TL (2), TMemo (4), Certificate (Box-folder 051:001)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN - GENERAL, 1960 - 1968, TDoc (16), TL (19), TMemo (8), Flyer (Box-folder 051:002)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE CAMPAIGN - GENERAL, 1955 - 1959, TDoc (7), TL (2), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 051:003)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE CAMPAIGN, 1954 - 1955, TDoc (46), TL (3), Newclipping (6), TMemo (6) (Box-folder 051:004)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE - GENERAL, 1953 - 1954, TDoc (17), TMemo (2), Offprint, Newsclipping (10) (Box-folder 051:005)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE CAMPAIGN - GENERAL, 1952 - 1953, TL (4), AL, TDoc (24), TMemo (5) (Box-folder 051:006)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE - GENERAL, 1951 - 1952, TDoc (13), TMemo (10) (Box-folder 051:007)
- CONGRESS OF INDUSTRIAL ORGANIZATIONS - VIRGINIA, 1950 - 1958, TDoc (7), TL, Brochure (10) (Box-folder 051:008)
- CHRONIC OBSTRUCTIVE PULMONARY DISEASE, 1975 - 1976, TL (3), Brochure (Box-folder 051:009)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, N. D., TDocs (Box-folder 052:001)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, N. D., TDocs (Box-folder 052:002)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, N. D., TDocs (Box-folder 052:003)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1915, TDocs (Box-folder 052:004)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1916, TDocs (Box-folder 052:005)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1917, TDocs (Box-folder 052:006)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1918, TDocs (Box-folder 052:007)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1919, TDocs (Box-folder 052:008)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1920, TDocs (Box-folder 052:009)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1921, TDocs (Box-folder 052:010)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1923, TDocs (Box-folder 052:012)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1922, TDocs (Box-folder 052:011)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1924, TDocs (Box-folder 052:013)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1925, TDocs (Box-folder 052:014)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1926, TDocs (Box-folder 052:015)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1927, TDocs (Box-folder 052:016)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1928, TDocs (Box-folder 052:017)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1929, TDocs (Box-folder 052:018)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1930, TDocs (Box-folder 052:019)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1931, TDocs (Box-folder 052:020)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1932, TDocs (Box-folder 052:021)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1933, TDocs (Box-folder 052:022)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1934, TDocs (Box-folder 052:023)
- CIRCULAR LETTER, 1935, TDocs (Box-folder 053:001)
- CIRCULAR LETTER, 1936, TDocs (Box-folder 053:002)
- CIRCULAR LETTER, 1937, TDocs (Box-folder 053:003)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1938, TDocs (Box-folder 053:004)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1939, TDocs (Box-folder 053:005)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1940, TDocs (Box-folder 053:006)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1941, TDocs (Box-folder 053:007)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1942, TDocs (Box-folder 053:008)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1943, TDocs (Box-folder 053:009)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1944, TDocs (Box-folder 053:010)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1945, TDocs (Box-folder 053:011)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1946, TDocs (Box-folder 053:012)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1947, TDocs (Box-folder 053:013)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1948, TDocs (Box-folder 053:014)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1949, TDocs (Box-folder 053:015)
- CIRCULAR LETTERS, 1950, TDocs (Box-folder 053:016)
- VTA COMMITTEE MINUTES, 1953 - 1954, TMemo, TDocs (25) (Box-folder 054:001)
- VTA COMMITTEE MINUTES, 1952 - 1953, TDoc (19) (Box-folder 054:002)
- VTA COMMITTEE MINUTES, 1951 - 1952, TDoc (19) (Box-folder 054:003)
- COMMITTEE ON TB ERADICATION, 1966 - 1968, TL (27), TDoc (10), TMemo (12), ADoc (Box-folder 054:004)
- COMMITTEE ON TB ERADICATION, 1969, TL (24), TDoc (7), TMemo (4), Pamphlets (4) (Box-folder 054:005)
- COMMITTEE ON TB AND 5 RD NURSING, 1964 - 1966, TDoc (3), TL (7), TMemo (11) (Box-folder 054:006)
- MATERIALS REGARDING SOLICITATION, VA, 1978 - 1979, TDoc (4), TL (4), Pamphlet (2) (Box-folder 054:007)
- SOLICITATION MATERIALS, VA, 1980 - 1981, TDoc (5), TL (5), TMemo (2) (Box-folder 054:008)
- COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA, 1979 - 1980, TL (3), TDoc (2) (Box-folder 054:009)
- COLLEGE HEALTH MEETING, 1958, TDoc (10), TL (6), Pamphlet, Newsclipping (4), Reprint (Box-folder 055:001)
- COLLEGE CONFERENCE ON HEALTH AND PHYSICAL EDUCATION, 1949 - 1952, TDocs (6), TL (2) (Box-folder 055:002)
- TUBERCULOSIS/CHRISTMAS SEAL ACTIVITIES: CLUBS, LODGES, SOCIETIES, 1918 - 1948, TL (17), TMemo (2), Newsclipping (Box-folder 055:003)
- COLLEGE HEALTH COMMITTEE, 1957 - 1958, TL (18), TDoc (3), TMemo (3), Newsclipping (2) (Box-folder 055:004)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL COLORING SHEETS, 1960 - 1968, TDocs (9), AMemos (2) (Box-folder 055:005)
- COMMITTEE OF ASSOCIATIONS, 1974 - 1976, TDocs (7), TMemo (5), TL (6) (Box-folder 055:006)
- COMMITTEE OF ASSOCIATIONS, 1970 - 1974, TDocs (24), TMemo (18), TL (5) (Box-folder 055:007)
- COMMITTEE ON ORGANIZATION, 1971 - 1974, TDoc (4) (Box-folder 055:008)
- COMMITTEE MINUTES, VTA, VOLUME 5, 1955 - 1956, Pamphlet, TDoc (24) (Box-folder 055:009)
- VIRGINIA TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION COMMITTEE MINUTES, 1954 - 1957, TDoc (25) (Box-folder 055:010)
- COMMITTEE MINUTES - VTA, 1954 - 1957, TDoc (21) (Box-folder 055:011)
- VIRGINIA LUNG ASSOCIATION COMMITTEE ROSTERS, 1974 - 1980, TDoc (5) (Box-folder 055:012)
- COMMUNICATIONS COUNCILS - GENERAL, 1958 - 1964, TDoc (10), TL (2), TMemo (14) (Box-folder 057:001)
- COMMUNITY ACTION PROGRAM, 1971 - 1972, TDoc (Box-folder 057:002)
- COMMUNITY HEALTH & WELFARE COMMITTEE MEETING MINUTES, 1971 - 1973, TDoc (4) (Box-folder 057:003)
- COMMUNITY HEALTH AND WELFARE, 1971 - 1974, TDoc (13) (Box-folder 057:004)
- COMMUNITY HEALTH AND WELFARE PROGRAM EMPHASIS, 1971 - 1974, Brochure (2) (Box-folder 057:005)
- COMMUNITY COUNCIL AND COMMUNITY FUND, 1941 - 1949, TDoc (24), TMemo, TL (Box-folder 057:006)
- COMPREHENSIVE HEALTH PLANNING, 1970 - 1971, TDoc (Box-folder 057:007)
- CONFERENCE ON EMPHYSEMA, 1967, TDoc (8), TLS (7), TMemo (Box-folder 057:008)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1980 - 1981, TDoc, Brochure, TMemo, TLS, Magazine (Box-folder 057:009)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1979 - 1980, TMemo (14), TL (4), TDoc (14) (Box-folder 057:010)
- HANDBOOK ON PROFESSIONAL STAFF DEVELOPMENT, 1980, Booklet (Box-folder 057:011)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1977 - 1979, TMemo (2), TL (2), TDoc (2) (Box-folder 057:012)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF MEMBERSHIP ROSTER, 1977, TDoc (Box-folder 057:013)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1976 - 1977, TDoc (3), TLS (8), Brochure, TMemo (12), ANote (Box-folder 058:001)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1975 - 1976, TDoc (16), TLS (10), TMemo (12) (Box-folder 058:002)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF MEMBERSHIP ROSTER, 1976, TDoc (Box-folder 058:003)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1974 - 1975, TMemo (5), TDoc (3), TLS (Box-folder 058:004)
- HANDBOOK ON PROFESSIONAL STAFF DEVELOPMENT, 1975, TDoc (Box-folder 058:005)
- CONGRESS OF LUNG ASSOCIATION STAFF, 1972 - 1974, TMemo (4), TL (2), TDoc (7), Brochure (2) (Box-folder 058:006)
- NATIONAL RESPIRATORY DISEASE CONFERENCE MEMBERSHIP ROSTER, 1972, TDoc (Box-folder 058:007)
- CONSERVATION COUNCIL OF VIRGINIA, 1969 - 1972, TL (6), TDoc (13) (Box-folder 058:008)
- CONSTITUTION AND BYLAWS COMMITTEE, 1978 - 1979, TDoc (5), TL (4) (Box-folder 058:009)
- CONSTITUTION AND BYLAWS COMMITTEE, 1960 - 1969, TDoc (10), TMemo (6), Brochure (3) (Box-folder 058:010)
- CONSTITUTION AND BYLAWS COMMITTEE, 1953 - 1960, TL (7), TMemo (6), TDoc (5), Brochure (2) (Box-folder 058:011)
- CHRISTMAS SEALS, - 1949 (Box-folder 059:001)
- SUGGESTED CONSTITUTION & BYLAWS WITH COMMENTS, 1948 - 1949, TDoc (Box-folder 059:002)
- VIRGINIA TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION BY-LAWS & CONSTITUTION, - 1949, TMemo (2), TDoc (2) (Box-folder 059:003)
- VTA BY-LAWS, 1947 - 1948, Brochures (5) (Box-folder 059:004)
- CONTRACTS, 1950 - 1960, TDoc (11), TMemo (2) (Box-folder 059:005)
- DUTIES AND QUALIFICATIONS OF TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVES, 1953, Brochure (Box-folder 059:006)
- APPOINTMENT OF AGENT FOR AUTHORIZED WORK FOR CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, 1951 - 1959, Brochures (8) (Box-folder 059:007)
- CONTRACTS FROM CONSTITUENT ASSOCIATIONS, 1954 - 1955, TDoc (10) (Box-folder 059:008)
- CONTRACTS FROM CONSTITUENT ORGANIZATIONS, 1946 - 1955, TL (8), TDoc (7), Brochure (Box-folder 059:009)
- CONTRACTS WITH LOCAL VIRGINIA TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATIONS, 1917 - 1949, ADoc, TDoc (21), TL (3) (Box-folder 059:010)
- CONTESTS, ESSAYS, PLAYS, POSTERS, ETC., 1936 - 1948, TDoc (15), TL (10), TMemo (5), Newsclipping (Box-folder 060:001)
  NEGRO ESSAY CONTESTS
- ESSAYS FROM CONTESTS, 1941 - 1943, TDoc (7), ADoc (5) (Box-folder 060:002)
- PLAYS FROM CONTESTS, 1931 - 1949, TDoc (6) (Box-folder 060:003)
- ESSAY CONTESTS - CORRESPONDENCE, 1941 - 1948, TDoc (7), TL (8), TMemo (Box-folder 060:004)
- CONTRACTS WITH LOCAL VIRGINIA TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATIONS, 1925 - 1949, TL (7), TDoc (11), TMemo (Box-folder 060:005)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL CONTRACTS WITH LOCAL AGENCIES, 1925 - 1949, TDoc (15) (Box-folder 060:006)
- THE RELATION OF AN EXECUTIVE SECRETARY TO HIS BOARD OF DIRECTORS AND EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE BY CHARLES HATFIELD, 1927, TDoc (Box-folder 060:008)
- CONTRACTS WITH NATIONAL TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION FOR CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, 1919- 1949, TDoc (28) (Box-folder 060:008)
- CONTRACT REVISION MATERIAL, - 1949, TDoc (3) (Box-folder 060:009)
- FACTORS ACCOUNTING FOR THE HIGH TUBERCULOSIS DEATH RATE IN VIRGINIA AND THEIR CONTROL BY BEATRIX FLEMING LAWSON, 1937, TDoc (Box-folder 060:010)
- ESSAY CONTEST ON TUBERCULOSIS, 1924 - 1935, TDoc (9), TL, Brochure (Box-folder 060:011)
- CONTEST CORRESPONDENCE, 1919 - 1949, TDoc (12), TL (39) (Box-folder 060:012)
- ESSAYS, - 1949, ADoc (12), TDoc (9), Drawing (Box-folder 061:001)
- ESSAYS, - 1949, TL, TDoc (4), ADoc (3) (Box-folder 061:002)
- ESSAYS, 1939 - 1949, TDoc (8), ADoc (3) (Box-folder 061:003)
- CONTRACT REVISION MATERIAL, - 1949, TMemo (2) TDoc (24), TL (11) (Box-folder 061:004)
- APPRAISAL FORM FOR LOCAL TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION, 1941, Booklet (3) (Box-folder 061:005)
- CONTRIBUTIONS, DONATIONS AND APPROPRIATIONS BY VTA TO OTHER ORGANIZATIONS, 1929 - 1938, TDoc (6), TL (2) (Box-folder 061:006)
- CONTRIBUTIONS, DONATIONS AND LEGACIES TO VIRGINIA TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION, 1919 - 1949, TDoc (3), TL (39), 8x10 B&W Photo (Box-folder 061:007)
- COOPERATIVE EDUCATION ASSOCIATION, - 1949, TDoc, Brochure (5) (Box-folder 061:008)
- REGISTER OF COPYRIGHTS, 1958 - 1963, TDoc (5), TL (Box-folder 061:009)
- REGISTER OF COPYRIGHTS FOR CHILDREN'S HEALTH CIRCULAR - CORRESPONDENCE, 1958 - 1963, TL (36) (Box-folder 061:010)
- COUNCIL OF ASSOCIATIONS, 1977 - 1980, TDoc (17), TLS (9), TMemo (11) (Box-folder 062:001)
- COUNCIL OF ORGANIZATIONS FOR THE HANDICAPPED, 1976, TDoc (Box-folder 062:002)
- CRAFT CHATTER, November 1962, TDoc (Box-folder 062:003)
- HOSPITAL FOR CRIPPLED CHILDREN, 1917, TL (9) (Box-folder 062:004)
- CROSS & SEAL, 1970 - 1972, TDoc (45) (Box-folder 062:005)
- CROSS & SEAL, 1969 - 1970, TDoc (19) (Box-folder 062:006)
- CROSS & SEAL, 1955 - 1962, TDoc (34) (Box-folder 062:007)
- CROSS & SEAL, 1952 - 1955, TDocs (Box-folder 062:008)
- CROSS & SEAL, 1964 - 1981, TL (10) (Box-folder 062:009)
- DADE COUNTY TB ASSOCIATION, 1961 - 1962, TL, TDoc, TMemo (2) (Box-folder 062:010)
- DAVIDSON, JESSE L. (WILL OF), 1981, TDoc, TL (3) (Box-folder 062:011)
- DIRECTORY OF NTA ORGANIZATIONAL STRUCTURE, FUNCTION AND PERSONNEL, May 1967, bound booklet (Box-folder 062:012)
- HISTORICAL DIRECTORY OF LOCAL, STATE & NATIONAL TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATIONS IN THE UNITED STATES, February 1945, TDoc (Box-folder 062:013)
- DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA TB ASSOCIATION, 1955 - 1963, TL (19), Booklet, TDoc (2), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 062:014)
- COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA DELEGATES TO CONVENTIONS, 1924, TL, Certificate (Box-folder 063:001)
- ORIGIN OF THE DOUBLE BARRED CROSS, - 1949, TDoc (9) (Box-folder 063:002)
- DEMONSTRATIONS: EXECUTIVE SECRETARIES FOR LOCAL ASSOCIATIONS, - 1949, AL (3), TDoc (3), TL (100) (Box-folder 063:003)
- DEMONSTRATIONS: EXECUTIVE SECRETARIES FOR LOCAL ASSOCIATIONS, - 1949, TMemo, TL (111), TDoc (6) (Box-folder 063:004)
- DEMONSTRATIONS: REHABILITATION & OTHER PROGRAMS, - 1949, TDoc (2), TL (84), TMemo (Box-folder 063:005)
- REPORT OF EXECUTIVE SECRETARY, 1942, TDoc (Box-folder 063:006)
- DVR-VLA JOINT PROJECT FOR THE SEVERLY HANDICAPPED, 1974 - 1975, TL (37) (Box-folder 063:007)
- DVR-VLA JOINT PROJECT FOR THE SEVERLY HANDICAPPED, 1974 - 1975, TDoc (3), Pamphlet (13) (Box-folder 063:008)
- DVR - VLA JOINT PROJECT FOR THE SEVERLY HANDICAPPED, 1974 - 1975, TDoc (28) (Box-folder 063:009)
- DVR - VTA JOINT PROJECT FOR THE SEVERLY HANDICAPPED, 1974 - 1975, TDoc (47) (Box-folder 063:010)
- DIAGNOSTIC STANDARDS, 1950 - 1964, TMemo (4), TDoc (2), TL (15), AL, Newsletter, Booklet (Box-folder 064:001)
- E. CATO DRASH, M.D., 1961 - 1970, TL (7), Newsclipping (2), TDoc (2), TMemo (Box-folder 064:002)
- DRUGS - DERIVATIVES OF ISONICOTINIC ACID RIMIFRON AND NYDRAZID, 1952 - 1967, TL (13), Pamphlet, TMemo (2), TDoc (2), Reprint (2) (Box-folder 064:003)
- DUKE UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTRE *WHAT GOES ON*, 1958 - 1964, Pamphlets (Box-folder 064:004)
- EARL DUNKLEE, 1954 - 1955, TL (4), ADoc, TMemo (15), TDoc, AL, Invitation (Box-folder 064:005)
- ESTATE OF BEATRICE DUNN, 1978, TL (11), TDoc (2) (Box-folder 064:006)
- EASTERN VIRGINIA MEDICAL SCHOOL, 1970 - 1980, TL (49), TDoc (21) (Box-folder 064:007)
- EASTERN VIRGINIA STUDY GROUP, 1950 - 1951, TL, TDoc (16), Tmemo (3) (Box-folder 064:008)
- EDUCATIONAL CHARTS, - 1949, TDoc, Charts (8), TL (4) (Box-folder 064:009)
- EDUCATIONAL MATERIALS, - 1949, TDoc, Pamphlets, Offprints (Box-folder 064:010)
- EFFECTIVE BUYING INCOME, 1952, TDoc, TMemo (Box-folder 064:011)
- EMPLOYMENT CORRESPONDENCE, 1916 - 1949, TDoc (10), TL (54), Telegram (4) (Box-folder 065:001)
- YOUR TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION REPORT, 1947 - 1948, Booklet (Box-folder 065:002)
- ENDORSMENTS AND COMMENDATIONS, - 1950, TL (24) (Box-folder 065:003)
- ENDORSEMENTS FOR VTA OFFICE, - 1950, TL (31), TDoc (25) (Box-folder 065:004)
- NOMINATING COMMITTEE, 1950, TForm (24) (Box-folder 065:005)
- THIRTY SEVENTH ANNUAL REPORT - VTA, 1948, Booklet (Box-folder 065:006)
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH MRS. HERBERT HOOVER, 1931, TL (4) (Box-folder 065:007)
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH GOVERNOR H. C. STUART, 1915, TL (4) (Box-folder 065:008)
- EQUALIZATION FUND, 1951 - 1952, TDoc (6), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 065:009)
- ANTI AIR POLLUTION CAMPAIGN, 1971 (Box-folder 065:010)
- ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH AWARDS PROGRAM, 1971 - 1974, TDoc (4), TMemo (6) (Box-folder 065:011)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1980 - 1981, TMemo (15), TDoc (2) (Box-folder 066:001)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1979 - 1980, TL, TDoc (12), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 066:002)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1978 - 1979, TDoc (22), TL (2), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 066:003)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1977 - 1978, TDoc (9), TMemo (Box-folder 066:004)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1976 - 1977, TL (2), TDoc (7), TMemo (5) (Box-folder 066:005)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1975 - 1976, TDoc (7), TMemo (3) (Box-folder 066:006)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1974 - 1975, TMemo 98), TL (4), TDoc (25) (Box-folder 066:007)
- VLA PROGRAM OF WORK, 1974 - 1975, Brochures (2) (Box-folder 066:008)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1973 - 1974, TL, TDoc (16), TMemo (3) (Box-folder 067:001)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1972 - 1973, TDoc (29), TMemo (3) (Box-folder 067:002)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1971 - 1972, TDoc (17), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 067:003)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1970 - 1971, TDoc (14), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 067:004)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1969 - 1970, TDoc (27), TL (2), TMemo (7) (Box-folder 067:005)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1968 - 1969, TDoc (16), TMemo (2), TL (3) (Box-folder 067:006)
- GUIDELINES AND POLICY MANUALS, 1973, Brochures (2) (Box-folder 067:007)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1967 - 1968, TMemo (8), TL, TDoc (36) (Box-folder 068:001)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1966 - 1967, TMemo (6), TDoc (17) (Box-folder 068:002)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1965 - 1966, TDoc (15), TMemo (7) (Box-folder 068:003)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1964 - 1965, TDoc (17), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 068:004)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1963 - 1964, TDoc (12), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 068:005)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1962 - 1963, TDoc (22), TLS, TMemo (5) (Box-folder 068:006)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1961 - 1962, TDoc (19), TMemo (3) (Box-folder 069:001)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1960 - 1961, TDoc (11), TMemo (3), TL (Box-folder 069:002)
- REPORT OF THE VIRGINIA CONFERENCE ON TUBERCULOSIS, September 1-4, 1960, TDoc (Box-folder 069:003)
- VTA: PROGRAM AND BUDGET, 1961 - 1962, TDoc (Box-folder 069:004)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1959 - 1960, TDoc (15), TMemo (7), TL (Box-folder 069:005)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1958 - 1959, TL (2), TDoc (7), TMemo (5) (Box-folder 069:006)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1957 - 1958, TDoc (13), TMemo (3) (Box-folder 069:007)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1956 - 1957, TDoc (11), TMemo (5) (Box-folder 069:008)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1955 - 1956, TDoc (22), TMemo (9), TL (5) (Box-folder 070:001)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1954 - 1955, TL (5), TDoc (13), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 070:002)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1951 - 1954, TDoc (21) (Box-folder 070:003)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1952 - 1953, TDoc (18), TMemo (3), TL (Box-folder 070:004)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1951 - 1952, TDoc (11), TMemo (11) (Box-folder 070:005)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1950 - 1951, TDoc (15), TMemo (8), TL (13), Invitation (Box-folder 070:006)
- EXHIBITS, 1951 - 1969, TL (22), B&W Photo 8x10 (2), Color Drawing, TDoc (6) (Box-folder 071:001)
- EXHIBITS, - 1949, TMemo (2), Booklet, TDoc (7), Newsclipping (11) (Box-folder 071:002)
- E GENERAL, 1959 - 1967, TL (5), AL, TDoc, Newsclipping (Box-folder 071:003)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE, 1957 - 1961, TL (4), TDoc (9), TMemo, Newsclipping (2) (Box-folder 071:004)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE MINUTES, 1952 - 1959, TDoc (13) (Box-folder 071:005)
- FACTI FINDING COMMITTEE: STUDY OF TB IN VIRGINIA, 1957 - 1958, TDocs (Box-folder 071:006)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE: CASE FINDING SUB-COMMITTEE, 1956 - 1957, TDoc (15), TL (10), TMemo (5) (Box-folder 071:007)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE, 1956 - 1957, TDoc (14), TMemo (8) (Box-folder 071:008)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE, 1955 - 1956, TDoc (9) (Box-folder 071:009)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE, 1954 - 1955, TDoc (15), TL (2), Booklet (Box-folder 072:001)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE, 1952 - 1954, TDoc (6), TL (13) (Box-folder 072:002)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE SURVEYS, 1952, TDoc (4), TMemo, TL (Box-folder 072:003)
- FACT FINDING COMMITTEE, 1952 - 1957, TL (6), Booklet, TDoc (13), TMemo (4) (Box-folder 072:004)
- FACT SHEET ON TUBERCULOSIS, 1954 - 1955, TDoc (Box-folder 072:005)
- FAKE CURES (TREATMENT), - 1949, Booklet (Box-folder 072:006)
- FALL CONFERENCE: MEETING IN RICHMOND, October 16 - 17, 1952, TDoc (15), TMemo (2), Booklets (2), TL (3) (Box-folder 072:007)
- FAIRS, 1954 - 1958, TDoc (4), ADoc, TL (11), TMemo (Box-folder 072:008)
- FEDERAL SERVICE CAMPAIGN FOR NATIONAL HEALTH AGENCIES, 1967, TDoc (11), TL (7), TMemo, Booklet (Box-folder 072:009)
- FEDERAL SERVICE CAMPAIGN FOR NATIONAL HEALTH AGENCIES, 1958 - 1959, TDoc (20), Booklet (2) (Box-folder 072:010)
- FEDERAL SERVICE CAMPAIGN FOR NATIONAL HEALTH AGENCIES, 1956-1959, TDoc (Box-folder 073:001)
- FEDERATED FUND RAISING, 1950-1951, TDoc (Box-folder 073:002)
- FIELD VISITS, 1947-1948, TDoc (Box-folder 073:003)
- FILING GUIDE, 1959-1962, TDoc (1) (Box-folder 073:004)
- FILMS, 1959-1967, TDoc, Brochure (Box-folder 073:005)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, -1949, TDoc (Box-folder 073:006)
- FINANCE COMMITTEE, 1961-1970, TDoc (Box-folder 073:007)
- FINANCIAL CHARTS, -1949, TDoc (Box-folder 073:008)
- FINANCIAL REPORTS, 1950, TDoc (Box-folder 073:009)
- VTA: FINANCIAL REPORTS, -1949, TDoc (Box-folder 073:010)
- FINANCIAL DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE, 1979-1980, TMem, TDoc (Box-folder 074:001)
- FINANCIAL DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE, 1975-1979, TDoc (Box-folder 074:002)
- FINANCIAL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1977-1981, TDoc (Box-folder 074:003)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, 1953, TDoc (Box-folder 074:004)
- FINANCIAL STATEMENTS, 1950-1952, TDoc (3) (Box-folder 074:005)
- GUIDE FOR TB FOLLOW UP FROM FLORIDA STATE BOARD OF HEALTH, 1958, TDoc (1) (Box-folder 074:006)
- FLORIDA TB & RD ASSOCIATION, 1960-1969, TDoc (Box-folder 074:007)
- ALLEN WEIR FREEMAN, 1954-1955, TDoc (Box-folder 075:001)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - AWARD NOMINATIONS, 1978-1981, TDoc (Box-folder 075:002)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - AWARD NOMINATIONS, 1971-1978, TDoc (Box-folder 075:003)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - AWARD NOMINATIONS, 1966-1974, TDoc (Box-folder 075:004)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - AWARD NOMINATIONS, 1960-1965, TDoc (Box-folder 075:005)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - AWARD NOMINATIONS, 1954-1959, TDoc (Box-folder 075:006)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - JURY, 1969-1977, TDoc (Box-folder 075:007)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - JURY, 1957-1971, TL, TDoc, TMem (Box-folder 075:008)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - AWARD NOMINATIONS, 1953-1954, TDoc (Box-folder 076:001)
- FREEMAN, DOUGLAS SOUTHALL - JURY, 1955-1956, TDoc (Box-folder 076:002)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 1 GENERAL SERIES: THE PROGRAM, 1920, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:003)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 2 MEDICAL SERIES: THE SICKNESS CURES, 1918, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:004)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 3 SANITARY SERIES: VITAL STATISTICS, August 1918, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:005)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 4 MEDICAL SERIES: MEDICAL EXAMINATION CAMPAIGNS, November 1918, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:006)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 5 MEDICAL SERIES: TUBERCULOSIS FINDINGS, March 1919, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:007)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 6 SANITARY SERIES: SCHOOLS AND FACTORIES, September 1919, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:008)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 8 GENERAL SERIES: HEALTH LETTERS, December 1920, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:009)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH SERIES NO. 7 THE CHILDREN'S SUMMER CAMP WITH SUPPLEMENT ON HOME LIVING CONDITIONS, May 1920, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:010)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 9 INFLUENZA: FRAMINGHAM EPIDEMIC & POST EPIDEMIC OBSERVATIONS, July 1922, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:011)
- FRAMINGHAM MONOGRAPH NO. 10 FINAL SUMMARY REPORT: 1917-1923 INCLUSIVE, July 1924, Book (1) (Box-folder 076:012)
- FUND RAISING COMMITTEE, 1972-1974, TDoc (Box-folder 076:013)
- FUND RAISING - VIRGINIA, 1959-1980, TDoc (Box-folder 076:014)
- FUND RAISING - VIRGINIA, 1958-1959, TDoc (Box-folder 076:015)
- FUND RAISING - VIRGINIA, 1956-1958, TDoc (Box-folder 076:016)
- FUNDRAISING - VIRGINIA, 1954-1956, TDoc, TL (Box-folder 076:017)
- FUND RAISING, 1949-1953, TLs(4),TL(9),TD(9),Pam(2),Info.kit(1),newsclip(3) (Box-folder 077:001)
- FUNDRAISING MATERIALS, 1951-1952, TL(7),TDoc(12),Pam(1),Newscl(9) (Box-folder 077:002)
- GENERAL HOSPITAL ADMISSIONS, 1955-1957, TD(35), TL(5) (Box-folder 077:003)
- HOSPITAL ADMISSIONS, 1954-1955, TD(17),TL(4),Pam(1),Nwsclp(1) (Box-folder 077:004)
- X-RAY LITERATURE - GENERAL HOSPITAL ADMISSION, 1949-1953, TD(6),TL(1),Journal(3),Pam(2) (Box-folder 077:005)
- GENERAL HOSPITAL ADMISSION - QUESTIONNAIRE, 1952, Approx. 150 Questionnaires (Box-folder 077:006)
- GENERAL HOSPITAL ADMISSIONS - X-RAYS, 1951-1952, TD(19),TL(14),Nclip(1),notes (Box-folder 077:007)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON EMPLOYMENT OF THE HANDICAPPED, 1977-1978, TLs(2),Pam(1),TD(2) (Box-folder 077:008)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON EMPLOYMENT OF THE HANDICAPPED, 1974-1977, TD(11),TL(3),TM(3),TLs(1),Rpt.(1),Pam(10) (Box-folder 077:009)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON THE EMPLOYMENT OF THE HANDICAPPED, 1969-1973, TL(4),Pam(6),TD(6),Rept.(1),TM(2) (Box-folder 077:010)
- NORA SPENCER HAMNER AWARD JURY, 1974-1975, TD(4) (Box-folder 077:011)